<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boxi Lin</title>
    <link>https://boxilin.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Boxi Lin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boxilin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://boxilin.github.io/posts/reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boxilin.github.io/posts/reading-list/</guid>
      <description> To explain or to predict? - Galit Shmueli Common statistical tests are linear models (or: how to teach stats), 中文版 因果革命 - 于淼 Combining p-values via averaging - Vladimir Vovk, Ruodu Wang Sensitivity Analysis in Observational Research: Introducing the E-Value How to finish a Ph.D. - Matthias Schonlau  动手学深度学习 Geometric Representation of High Dimension, Low Sample Size Data The cancer genome A tutorial on conducting genome‐wide association studies: Quality control and statistical analysis  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://boxilin.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boxilin.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Boxi Lin. I am interested in computational statistics and genetic data analysis.
Currently I am pursuing Ph.D. in Biostatistics at the University of Toronto, under the supervision of Lei Sun. Before that I completed my M.Math and B.Math in Statistics at the University of Waterloo, supervised by Pengfei Li.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://boxilin.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boxilin.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: boxi.lin[at]mail.utoronto.ca</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://boxilin.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boxilin.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Submitted Lin, B., and Sun, L., Better together against genetic effect heterogeneity: a sex-combined interaction analysis of testosterone levels in the UK Biobank data
Lin, B., Gong, J., Panjwani, N., Keenan, K., Lin, F., Sun, L. and Strug, L., Genome-Wide Association Study of Susceptibility to Pseudomonas aeruginosa Infection in Cystic Fibrosis
Publication Yuan, M., Wang, C., Lin, B. and Li, P. (2022) Semiparametric inference on general functionals of two semicontinuous populations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>